As I look back on the mission that we've had here on the International Space Station,
I'm proud to have been a part of much of the science activities that happened over the
last two months.
The view is always amazing though.
I didn't think I would do another spacewalk and to now have the chance to have done four
more was just icing on the cake for a wonderful mission.
It's hard to put into words just what it was like to be a part of this expedition, Expedition
63.
It'll be kind of a memory that will last a lifetime for me.
It's been a true honor.
Dragon SpaceX, Undock sequence commanded.
The roster's looking good.
The hardest part was getting us launched, but the most important part is bringing us
home.
I've been telling Daddy we love you.
Hurry home so we can go get my dog.
Flashdown.
Welcome back to planet Earth and thanks for flying SpaceX.
It's truly our honor and privilege.
SpaceX dads are back on Earth after a 19 hour return journey from space.